<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
    Copyright 2012 Jonas Schürmann ©

    My Website: mazechazer.jimdo.com

    This file is part of  the WoT Tank Quiz.

    The WoT Tank Quiz is free software: you can redistribute it and/or modify
    it under the terms of the GNU General Public License as published by
    the Free Software Foundation, either version 3 of the License, or
    (at your option) any later version.

    The WoT Tank Quiz is distributed in the hope that it will be useful,
    but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
    MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the
    GNU General Public License for more details.

    You should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License
    along with the WoT Tank Quiz.  If not, see <http://www.gnu.org/licenses/>. -->
<resources>
    <string name="Play">Play</string>
    <string name="Level">Level</string>
    <string name="Highscore">Highscore</string>
    <string name="About">About</string>
    <string name="AboutText">This App has been programmed by Jonas Schürmann aka MazeChaZer.\nIt is free software (open source).\nFor further Information visit my website:\n\nmazechazer.jimdo.com\n\nThere you also have the possibility to contact me or to send me a bug report.\nI hope you have fun with this app :)\nIt would be cool if you could give me a feedback on the Google Play Store or on my website.\n\nLicense\nCopyright 2012 Jonas Schürmann ©\nThe WoT Tank Quiz is free software: you can redistribute it and/or modify it under the terms of the GNU General Public License as published by the Free Software Foundation, either version 3 of the License, or (at your option) any later version. The WoT Tank Quiz is distributed in the hope that it will be useful, but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the GNU General Public License for more details. You should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License along with the WoT Tank Quiz.  If not, see &lt;http://www.gnu.org/licenses/&gt;.\nThe images of the tanks are excluded from this licence, wargaming.net is the copyright holder of these. Pictures used with permission. \&quot;World of Tanks\&quot; is a registered trademark of wargaming.net.\nFor further information about licensing visit my web site.</string>
    <string name="Okay">okay</string>
    <string name="Easy">Easy</string>
    <string name="Medium">Medium</string>
    <string name="Hard">Hard</string>
    <string name="Points">Points</string>
    <string name="Time">Time</string>
    <string name="GamePaused">Game paused</string>
    <string name="Continue">Continue</string>
    <string name="BackToMenu">Back to menu</string>
    <string name="NewHighscore">New Highscore!</string>
    <string name="StatementLessThanZero">Haha you got less than zero points!</string>
    <string name="StatementZeroToTen">Not bad. Keep it up.</string>
    <string name="StatementElevenToTwenty">Well done.</string>
    <string name="StatementTwentyoneToThirty">Wow, good job.</string>
    <string name="StatementThirtyoneAndMore">WTF you\'re a freak :)</string>
    <string name="PleaseEnterYourName">Please enter your name</string>
    <string name="Changelog">Changelog</string>
    <string name="ChangelogText">Version 1.7\n•Added new tanks of the WoT 8.2 update: T21, T71, Т69, Т54E1, T57, TOG–2, АТ–15А, FCM 50t\n•Fixed rare bug that the text on the answer buttons wasn\'t readable on some devices\n\nVersion 1.6\n•Added new tanks of the WoT 8.1 update: SU–122–44, Panther M–10, PzKpfw IV Schmalturm, Cruiser MK. I, A13 Mk. I Cr. Tank Mk. III, A10 Cruiser Mk. II, A13 Mk. II Cr. Tank Mk. IV, Valentine Mk.III, A13 Covenanter, Crusader, Medium Mark I, Vickers Medium Mk. II, Vickers Medium Mk. III, Matilda, Cromwell, Comet, Centurion Mk. I, Centurion Mk. 7/1, FV4202(105), Churchill I, Churchill VII, Black Prince, Caernarvon, Conqueror, FV215b\n\nVersion 1.5\n•Added German and Spanish translations of the app\n•Added new tanks of the WoT updates:\n7.4: RenaultFT AC, Renault UE 57, Somua SAu–40, S–35 CA, ARL V39, AMX AC Mle.1946, AMX AC Mle.1948, AMX 50 Foch, RenaultBS, Lorraine39 L AM, AMX 105AM, AMX 13 F3 AM, Lorraine 155 50, Lorraine 155 51, Bat Chatillon 155, IS–6, Jagdtiger 8,8 cm PaK 43\n7.5: JagdPz E–100, Object 268, AMX–50 Foch (155), T110E3, T110E4, E–50 Ausf. M, T–62A, M48A1, ELC AMX, Dicker Max, Super Pershing\n8.0: SU–100М1, SU–101, SU–122–54, Object 263, Matilda Black Prince\n•Improved tank picking (no tank is picked twice anymore during one game)\n•Improved alternate answer picking (no more blank fields)\n•New header on the start page, new font for buttons\n•Added Button to show the Changelog in the \&quot;About\&quot;–Dialog\n\nVersion 1.4\n•Fixed bug that the \&quot;Changelog\&quot;–dialog isn\'t shown\n\nVersion 1.3\n•Added new tanks of the WoT 7.3 update: KV–1, KV–2, T–150, ST–I, IS–4, IS–8, Type 62 and WZ–111\n\nVersion 1.2.1 (Unofficial Release) \n•Fixed S–51 spelling mistake (\&quot;SU–51\&quot;)\n•Fixed bug around Hummel/Grille\n\nVersion 1.2\n•Removed countdown bug when the pause dialog was cancelled with the back button\n•Removed the bug that the pause dialog appears over the highscore dialog when activity is paused\n•Added the \&quot;Changelog\&quot;–notification\n•Fixed the Bug that the highscore dialog displays the wrong score finally\n\nVersion 1.1\n•Improvements in the App Icon\n•Fixed Bug that the highscore dialog displays the wrong score</string>
    
</resources>